[ {
  "user" : {
    "id" : "26c7fe3c-bb12-4e0f-bc74-ac5d285d3319",
    "userType" : "STUDENT",
    "username" : "Studentas",
    "password" : "Studentas",
    "name" : "Studentas",
    "surname" : "Studentas"
  },
  "exam" : {
    "id" : "93cac4af-ad14-48d6-8581-54ea2f44df4a",
    "examType" : "TEST",
    "name" : "OOP",
    "questions" : [ {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 2
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "c", "b", "a" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 1
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "b", "a", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 3
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "b", "a", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 3
    } ]
  },
  "answers" : [ 2, 1, 3, 1 ],
  "grade" : "8",
  "time" : "2022-05-11T18:41:34.339982900"
}, {
  "user" : {
    "id" : "26c7fe3c-bb12-4e0f-bc74-ac5d285d3319",
    "userType" : "STUDENT",
    "username" : "Studentas",
    "password" : "Studentas",
    "name" : "Studentas",
    "surname" : "Studentas"
  },
  "exam" : {
    "id" : "81201942-a291-4feb-aa98-a929140ae252",
    "examType" : "TEST",
    "name" : "OOP2",
    "questions" : [ {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 1
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "c", "b", "a" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 2
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "b", "a", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 3
    } ]
  },
  "answers" : [ 3, 2, 1 ],
  "grade" : "3",
  "time" : "2022-05-12T15:28:22.503180800"
}, {
  "user" : {
    "id" : "e1777c62-672d-4c90-bb07-7813245025c1",
    "userType" : "STUDENT",
    "username" : "Studentas2",
    "password" : "Studentas2",
    "name" : "Studentas2",
    "surname" : "Studentas2"
  },
  "exam" : {
    "id" : "93cac4af-ad14-48d6-8581-54ea2f44df4a",
    "examType" : "TEST",
    "name" : "OOP",
    "questions" : [ {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 2
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "c", "b", "a" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 1
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "b", "a", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 3
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "b", "a", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 3
    } ]
  },
  "answers" : [ 1, 1, 3, 1 ],
  "grade" : "5",
  "time" : "2022-05-12T15:30:58.126538400"
}, {
  "user" : {
    "id" : "3678b845-0bf1-49da-a94d-e6765d410b60",
    "userType" : "STUDENT",
    "username" : "Studentas3",
    "password" : "Studentas3",
    "name" : "Studentas3",
    "surname" : "Studentas3"
  },
  "exam" : {
    "id" : "81201942-a291-4feb-aa98-a929140ae252",
    "examType" : "TEST",
    "name" : "OOP2",
    "questions" : [ {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 1
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "c", "b", "a" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 2
    }, {
      "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
      "answers" : [ "b", "a", "c" ],
      "correctAnswer" : 3
    } ]
  },
  "answers" : [ 1, 3, 3 ],
  "grade" : "7",
  "time" : "2022-05-12T17:14:18.274250300"
} ]